NobitaLand, the City of Dreams
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi..me/OrangeFlash
Watch out!
I got this!
Yes, very good There. there..
Keep going!
Hey, watch out!
Doraemon, don't drop me.
Who in their right mind would play on skating board inside house?
But skating outside is more dangerous than inside...
True...
Do you wanna get hit, foolish kid?!
Oh no!
Huh, What happened, Shizuka-chan?
I wanted to play inside home once in a while.
But my mum is hosting a tea ceremony gathering with her friends...
So she told me to go out & play.
Yes, we will.
Wonderful! Let's do it.
Let's do it
Under construction
No Entry!
Huh? When did this get here?
Under construction
No Entry!
So we can't play? Tell me why!
Can't you undestand by seeing with your eyes?
They're going to construct, so it's no entry zone, you fool!
Sucks.
Then where are we supposed to play?
Hey! You didn't have to hit me!
I wish...
What?
An exclusive house...
An exclusive city...
Where I can freely do anything I wish...
I want such city where I can do anything I want to, without getting scolded by others!
A independent city, huh?
Alright, let's construct one!
What do you mean? Are we going to construct such a city?
First let's re-make our own house.
Polaroid Instant Mini footage Camera!
First shoot a photo...
then print it...
Pour some water on it!
Wait for a few secs.
Alright, it's all done.
A mini house, huh?
Wow, everything is made in detail.
But it's just a tiny toy.
No worries, we just have to shrink!
Oh, I see.
Wait, you mean it?
Enter this "Gulliver's Tunnel"
See? I shrank.
How interesting!
Nobita-kun, you too enter the Gulliver's tunnel and come inside this mini house.
I'm going to make lot of buildings!
Doraemon, now the city has become lively.
Now we can organize whatever and however we want.
A very tiny book!
The words written are the size of ants.
But what about the residents of each buildings?
Don't worry, they won't be present in the shots I took.
Let's have a street here!
But no traffic lights and zebra crossing?
Let's make a bowling gym and a baseball field.
Let's make a video game corner.
Doraemon, click more shots while I'm away!
I'll bring my friends!
Why are you so grinning while we're feeling bored?
So weird!
Guys, today I'll make your dreams come true!
Follow me!
I doubt that he's just sleep talking!
You'll pay if it was a bluff!
This is the entry point.
Don't fool us! How can we enter this?
Just follow me!
OMG!
it's awesome!
Let's make this our city.
ouch, it hurts
Let us join!
if you eat too much Dorayaki, you will have a stomach-ache, Dora-chan.
give me the toy model
Get whatever you want, suit yourself!
I have been dreaming to be laying down on the street and sleep like this.
I am tired of playing so I'll read a Manga.
Everyone is having fun of playing.
Let's call this place NobitaLand.
Oh no!
it's Mum
Help!
There is so much junk here.
Let's have a small warehouse here, please construct it for me. Will you?
Yes Ma'am!
This is the end for NobitaLand!
Say, Doraemon. Please pull out a gadget which could make some ground.
Please, I beg of you!
You'll pay a hard price, if you don't.
But it's just impossible to make up some ground.
Nobita, quickly clear up all this junk at once!
Doraemon, please.
No way!
Hey, come on! That's not fair!